Brother Gerard Matthew Weiss Papers
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
- 1. Family History as catalogued by Brother Gerard Matthew Weiss (see appendix for a transcription of the Weiss inventory), 1; 0.66 linear feet 1 - 2 1 - 16
  - Photographs numbered for the catalogue by Brother Weiss (Folder 16, Box 2)
    - P9a-e, not dated, photos of the Minnesota River, 8 (Box 2)
    - P10, not dated, photo of desk lamp, 9 (Box 2)
    - P11, not dated, photo of nook shelves and drawers, 10 (Box 2)
    - P12a-b, not dated, photos of Steve and John or John and Steve, 11 (Box 2)
    - P13, not dated, photo of William and his youngest girl, 12 (Box 2)
    - P14, not dated, photo of Lockhead in hanger, 13 (Box 2)
    - P15, not dated, photo of an airplane used for mail service on the field with a bi-plane beside it, 14 (Box 2)
    - P16, March 21, 1898, photo of Melvin at the age of 19 years, 15 (Box 2)
    - P17, 1921, picture of Mabel Jackson addressed to Orin, 16 (Box 2)
    - P19, July 31, 1899, photo of dog Bingo and Jim, 17 (Box 2)
    - P20, March 2, 1899, Mrs. Frank Rogers, 18 (Box 2)
    - P21, June 4, 1899, Family Portrait, 19 (Box 2)
    - P22, September 1898, photo of Flora McCall at the age of 15, 20 (Box 2)
    - P23, November 9, 1901, photo oh Jennie Henderson (mother) on her 45th birthday, 21 (Box 2)
    - P24, May 30, 1900, Bishop Rogers, 22 (Box 2)
    - P25, September 1901, photo taken in Hamilton, Minn., 23 (Box 2)
    - P26, April 1, 1899, Fred J. Fowler, 24 (Box 2)
    - P27, not dated, photo of Billy and his sister (Irish neighbors), 25 (Box 2)
    - P28, May 10, 1908, photo of Dr Henrie Lysne, 26 (Box 2)
    - P29, not dated, photo of Mery Youngs Plane, 27 (Box 2)
    - P30, not dated, John’s friend Margaret in front of Lockhead, 28 (Box 2)
    - P32, August 11, 1899, photo of May Clark and Chas. Henderson on the carriage road near the house, 29 (Box 2)
    - 89A, December 25, 1941, to Andrew and Edson from Ruth a homemade Christmas card with a few family photos inside, 30 (Box 2)
    - 89B, December 25, 1941, to Andrew and Edson from Ruth a homemade Christmas card with a few family photos inside, 31 (Box 2)
    - December 1879, Jennie Belle Henderson age 9 months, 32 (Box 2)
- 2. Additional Materials not identified in the inventory by Brother Weiss, 2; 0.33 linear foot 3 17 - 26
  Series contains letters, contracts, and photographs not numbered for the inventory by Brother Weiss.
  By Subject
  - Correspondence not numbered for inventory (Folder 17, Box 3)
  - Newspaper clippings not numbered for inventory (Folder 18, Box 3)
  - Newspaper clippings on local historical sites not numbered for inventory (Folder 19, Box 3)
  - Notebook for Jennie Henderson not numbered for inventory (Folder 20, Box 3)
  - Newspaper clippings on Marist College not numbered for inventory (Folder 21, Box 3)
  - Unidentified photographs (Folder 22, Box 3)
  - Unidentified Miscellaneous family photos (Folder 23, Box 3)
  - Unidentified Tin Types (Folder 24, Box 3)
  - Unidentified black and white portraits (Folder 25, Box 3)
  - Miscellaneous Black and White Photos (small, 2x2 - 2x4) (Folder 26, Box 3)
- 3. Appendix, 3